http://www.champgolf.com/pages/privacy-policy-champspikes-com

CHAMP® Elite™
Logger (Ice)
Close
$5 GROUND SHIPPING AVAILABLE ON ALL ORDERS.
VISIT OUR EU SITE
Cart (0)
CHAMP® Elite™
Logger (Ice)
Privacy Policy - Champspikes.com
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.champspikes.com.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone at anytime.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy, as it relates to www.champspikes.com.
Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted in a secure way using the payment gateways of www.paypal.com, and www.shopify.com.  You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
PayPal and Shopify use encryption to protect sensitive credit card information transmitted online and are well noted in the industry in having secure environments. Champspikes.com does not receive any credit card information, this is all done through the PayPal and Shopify payment gateways, and as a result Champspikes.com cannot be held responsible for any security breach that may occur.
Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information such as mailing and e-mail addresses are kept in a secure environment.
Updates Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via our Contact Form.
CHAMP SPIKES:
Copyright © 2020 Champspikes • All rights reserved.
